<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Python on </title>
    <link>https://anfe67.github.io/categories/python/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Python on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:40:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anfe67.github.io/categories/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VCARD QR Codes in Inkscape</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/qrcodes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:40:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/qrcodes/</guid>
      <description>A Inkscape plugin to generate VCARD QR Codes. This work is based on a inkscape plugin by Sergey Vedernikov, in turn based on the work of others.
My version is a little modification to the plugin that Sergey proposed in a Inkscape forum. I generate a VCARD (the plugin interface is consistent) that contains a field for the website and not the birthday of the contact.
In my opinion this is much better to use the plugin to generate QR Codes for business cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apprenons Python</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/app-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:35:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/app-python/</guid>
      <description>Apprenons Python Apprenons Python en jouant is a website I built to keep track of a trip into teaching Python programming to kids.
The site started as a way to respond to the innocent question from my son and one of his friends: How do you write a video game.
We started this trip a couple of years ago and since then we have explored the world of text based gaming, graphics based gaming, web development, physical computing (with the raspberry pi) etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science day by day</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/datascience-dbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:34:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/datascience-dbd/</guid>
      <description>Data Science day by day Data Science day by day is my Data Science learning blog. In 2015, I started learning about Data Science and ML, being a seasoned IT Professional it did not sound at all new to me. But I wanted to learn and to keep up to date with the most recent developments,
I wanted to brush up my stats and maths, I wanted to be current (or as current as I can).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>