<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordpress on </title>
    <link>https://anfe67.github.io/tags/wordpress/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wordpress on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 22:50:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anfe67.github.io/tags/wordpress/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speed Comparison</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/speed-comparison/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 22:50:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/speed-comparison/</guid>
      <description>Comparison of web technologies for speed (almost unoptimized) Not being a professional web developer, but just toying with the various technologies available, I just wanted to compare a few of them for what concerns pure speed. For this, I used the web site GTMetrix.
I run the test comparing five web sites, this one which is authored in Hugo, and a few others presented in other articles in these pages. The SaF IT Services is a simple Bootstrap single page web site, and the other three are wordpress sites, two of which are hosted on freely provided names and web space, also discussed here,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idées Suspendues</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/idees/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/idees/</guid>
      <description>Idées Suspendues The thema is the COVID-19 pandemy, and the will to restart in full safety. But we do not want the little economy, what we call the &amp;ldquo;Real&amp;rdquo; economy to die due to this virus.
The site can be reached at Idées Suspendues and this is the idea behind:

After the stores reopen, we all wonder how restaurants will be able to adapt to the new safety standards to welcome their customers again .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Science day by day</title>
      <link>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/datascience-dbd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 11:34:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anfe67.github.io/posts/datascience-dbd/</guid>
      <description>Data Science day by day Data Science day by day is my Data Science learning blog. In 2015, I started learning about Data Science and ML, being a seasoned IT Professional it did not sound at all new to me. But I wanted to learn and to keep up to date with the most recent developments,
I wanted to brush up my stats and maths, I wanted to be current (or as current as I can).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>